OK so now we have our poorly drawn cottage.
好的，现在我们有了画得很差的小屋。
You remember the word cottage.
你记得山寨这个词。
This is our cottage.
这是我们的小屋。
And hey the other word chimney.
嘿，另一个词烟囱。
There it is.
它在那里。
There is the chimney needs a little smoke.
有烟囱需要一点烟。
I think obviously smoke.
我认为显然是吸烟。
Smoke makes that sound right.
烟雾使听起来正确。
That's really not good smoke.
这真的不是好烟。
I'm sorry about being such a bad artist.
我很抱歉成为一个如此糟糕的艺术家。
I'm not an artist.
我不是艺术家。
I did my best.
我尽力了。
I did draw this all by myself.
这都是我自己画的。
All right.
好的。
So we have a cottage.
所以我们有一个小屋。
It's got a chimney a cottage it's got a chimney.
它有一个烟囱 一个小屋它有一个烟囱。
And what's the material we need to first pick out our adjectives and our main noun.
而我们首先需要什么材料来挑出我们的形容词和我们的主要名词。
Well why don't we just use cottage as our main noun.
那么我们为什么不直接使用山寨作为我们的主要名词。
Make it simple.
让它变得简单。
OK.
好的。
This is this will be r m n why not our M N will be our may now and then we have here.
这就是这将是 r m n 为什么不是我们的 M N 将是我们的可能，然后我们在这里。
What's it made of those look like.
那些看起来像什么。
It looks like stone right.
它看起来像石头。
OK so materials stone.
OK 所以材料石头。
Is it is it big or is it small.
是大还是小。
Was pretty simple it's pretty small.
很简单，它很小。
What feeling do I get when I look at this whole scene.
当我看到这整个场景时，我有什么感觉。
What is the atmosphere.
什么气氛。
Remember we talked about atmosphere earlier in the class the feeling we get from a place where the atmosphere
记得我们在课堂上早先谈到了气氛，我们从一个有气氛的地方得到的感觉
here is if I look at this scene little there's a little lake here that's supposed to be water lake some
如果我看一下这个场景，这里有一个小湖，应该是水湖
trees nothing else around.
周围没有其他树木。
Pretty lonely let's use lonely and where is it.
很寂寞让我们用寂寞，它在哪里。
Where is this place.
这个地方在哪。
Well it's let's just say it's in the countryside.
好吧，我们就说它在农村。
So we'll add countryside that's where it is and I'm gonna make countryside not the adjective for this
所以我们将添加农村，这就是它所在的地方，我要让农村不是这个的形容词
I'm going to make countryside where it all is.
我要让乡村成为一切。
So we'll use small stone lonely three adjectives and we'll use cottage.
所以我们将使用小石头孤独的三个形容词，我们将使用山寨。
Remember we used with four for the car we say with for what the cottage has it's got a it's got a roof
请记住，我们用四个来表示我们所说的汽车有什么小屋有它有一个它有一个屋顶
but it's kind of a special roof.
但它是一种特殊的屋顶。
Right.
正确的。
It's kind of a weird roof this kind of roof with straw on the top is called a thatched roof thatched.
这是一种奇怪的屋顶这种顶部有稻草的屋顶被称为茅草屋顶茅草屋顶。
I didn't mention this in the vocabulary at the start of the class because if you don't remember the
我没有在课程开始时的词汇表中提到这一点，因为如果你不记得
word fat.
胖字。
That's OK.
没关系。
It's not a really common word so let's just use fast as a way to describe the roof and it's obviously
这不是一个很常见的词，所以让我们用 fast 来描述屋顶，很明显
beside a lake.
在一个湖边。
So I think we can put thatched countryside.
所以我觉得我们可以把茅草放在乡下。
We can talk about the roof.
我们可以谈谈屋顶。
We can put all of this in our first sentence.
我们可以把所有这些都放在我们的第一句话中。
I will write it all down very clearly later on but we could say as our first sentence there is always
稍后我会非常清楚地写下来，但我们可以说，作为我们的第一句话，总是
a good way to begin a description of something you're looking at.
开始描述您正在查看的内容的好方法。
There is a small lonely stone cottage with a thatched roof thatched roof beside a lake beside a lake
湖边有一座孤零零的石屋，茅草屋顶，茅草屋顶
and we could say beside Blue Lake or we could add adjectives there to beside a lake in the countryside.
我们可以说在蓝湖旁边，或者我们可以在乡下的湖边加上形容词。
There is a small lonely stone cottage with a thatched roof beside a lake in the countryside.
在乡间的湖边，有一座孤零零的茅草屋顶的小石屋。
OK so that's a pretty simple first sentence again.
好的，这又是一个非常简单的第一句话。
I'll write it down in a little bit but that's a pretty easy way to describe it.
我会稍微写下来，但这是一种非常简单的描述方式。
And the picture that you get in your mind is very clear.
而你脑海中浮现的画面非常清晰。
But now we want to go further we want to describe the other things too.
但现在我们想更进一步，我们也想描述其他事情。
There's a lot more going on here.
这里还有很多事情要做。
What else does the cottage have.
小屋还有什么。
Well it has a square window there's a little a little square window it's a little square window small
嗯，它有一个方形的窗户有一个小方窗 这是一个小方窗 小
that's the size.
那是大小。
Don't use small again because we already said Small.
不要再使用 small，因为我们已经说过 Small。
And if you use small small small too many times that's not good.
如果你使用 small small small 太多次，那就不好了。
That's called repetition.
这叫重复。
We don't usually want repetition if you can use another word like teeny or little or something like
如果您可以使用其他词，例如 teeny 或 little 或类似的东西，我们通常不希望重复
that.
那。
That's often better because it's different.
这通常更好，因为它是不同的。
It sounds better.
听起来更好。
So little in the shape square window and that's at the front of the house.
方形窗户的形状很小，就在房子的前面。
So there's a little square window at the front and then beside that we can connect the door to the window
所以前面有一个小方形窗户，然后在旁边我们可以将门连接到窗户
and beside that beside what side the window beside that beside that is a single wooden door.
旁边那扇窗户旁边是一扇木门。
Wooden is the material.
木头是材料。
If you want to say wood that's a noun it is wood.
如果你想说木头是名词，那就是木头。
The adjective is wooden.
形容词是木制的。
A single one wooden door beside that right.
右边的一扇木门。
With now we can connect this little this little thing here.
现在我们可以在这里连接这个小东西。
This is called a let's call this a it's a path and an adjective for the path man.
这被称为a让我们称之为a它是一条路径，并且是路径人的形容词。
Maybe narrow and what's the material of the path.
也许狭窄，路径的材料是什么。
Well it's it's dirt it's a dirt it's a dirt path a DIY Artie.
嗯，它是泥土，它是泥土，它是一条 DIY Artie 的泥土路。
So notice that it's not only the first main noun that I'm adding more adjectives to I'm doing it for
所以请注意，我添加更多形容词的不仅仅是第一个主要名词，我正在这样做
several of them.
其中几个。
OK so there's a narrow dirt path that is leading away leading away from the from the front door or leading
好的，所以有一条狭窄的土路正在远离前门或通往
toward something leading away from means it begins there and goes away leading toward something is what
指向某物，远离意味着它从那里开始，然后离开，指向某物是什么
it's moving in the direction of.
它正朝着 的方向移动。
Now is the path really moving.
现在这条路真的在移动。
No it's not.
不，这不对。
But we can use that action to make it feel like it is right.
但是我们可以使用这个动作让它感觉它是正确的。
The road is winding up the mountain is it really the road is is just there right.
这条路蜿蜒上山，真的这条路就在那里。
Yes that's true.
是的，这是真的。
But the feeling of it is that it's winding its winding up the mountain it's winding its winding up the
但它的感觉是它在蜿蜒曲折的山上蜿蜒曲折
mountain.
山。
So that can really help us make the description that we have feel very active.
所以这真的可以帮助我们使我们感觉非常活跃的描述。
It's a really good way to describe things.
这是描述事物的一种非常好的方式。
So I've talked about the door the window the path the roof the chimney the the actual cottage itself
所以我谈到了门 窗 路径 屋顶 烟囱 实际的小屋本身
where it is.
在哪儿。
It's location.
它的位置。
We have a lot of information but I want to say a couple other things before I actually get to my my
我们有很多信息，但在我真正开始之前我想说几句
story part.
故事部分。
OK so what about the trees.
好的，那么树木呢。
So we could say that the tree is beside the house.
所以我们可以说树在房子旁边。
Right.
正确的。
We can use beside you could say beside the house there is right beside the house.
我们可以用beside you可以说beside the house there is right beside the house。
There is.
有。
Or if you want to make it a little bit more active you could say standing
或者如果你想让它更活跃一点，你可以说站立
standing beside the house there is.
站在房子旁边有。
Or standing beside the house is a tree.
或者站在房子旁边是一棵树。
And again we can try to make it more interesting by adding other adjectives.
再一次，我们可以尝试通过添加其他形容词使其更有趣。
This tree this tree here doesn't look very.
这棵树这棵树看起来不太好。
Doesn't look very healthy right.
看起来不太健康吧。
So let's use an interesting adjective let's use.
所以让我们使用一个有趣的形容词让我们使用。
I'm gonna use the adjective scraggly if I have room to write this I'll write it down at the bottom.
如果我有足够的空间来写这个，我会乱糟糟地使用形容词，我会写在底部
This is about the tree.
这是关于树的。
OK.
好的。
S C R A G G L Y.
S C R A G G L Y。
It's an interesting adjective to use a scraggly tree scraggly tree beside the house of standing beside
在站在旁边的房子旁边用一棵参差不齐的树是一个有趣的形容词
the house is a scraggly tree.
房子是一棵参差不齐的树。
But there's another tree.
但是还有一棵树。
Where's the tree.
树在哪里。
Well we could say that the tree is in the distance.
出色地我们可以说那棵树在远处。
We could say the distance or we could say in the background in the distance in the background.
我们可以说距离，或者我们可以说在背景中的距离在背景中。
So if you look at this other tree here it's in the distance and there's kind of a row of something here.
所以如果你看这里的另一棵树，它就在远处，这里有一排东西。
Let's call these bushes hedges.
我们把这些灌木称为树篱。
Let's call them hedges.
让我们称它们为对冲。
HEDGES HPD G.S. so we have one tree here at scraggly we have another in the distance and it's by a row
HEDGES HPD G.S. 所以我们这里有一棵参差不齐的树，我们在远处还有一棵树，它在一排
a row a row of hedges.
一排一排树篱。
So we kind of have all the pieces.
所以我们有点拥有所有的部分。
Now we want to put all the pieces together and then we want to use our imagination.
现在我们想把所有的部分放在一起，然后我们想发挥我们的想象力。
So what we're going to do next is I'm going to put all this into one clear description a few sentences
所以我们接下来要做的就是我要把这一切都放在一个清晰的描述中，几句话
and then I'm going to add what I think is going on in this picture a little bit of a story based on
然后我将添加我认为在这张照片中发生的一些故事
my own imagination.
我自己的想象。
What I would like to add but it's very important to understand and remember that when you're describing
我想添加的内容，但理解并记住您在描述时非常重要
first you start with the basic details.
首先，您从基本细节开始。
First you make clear sentences that have lots of information.
首先，你要写出包含大量信息的清晰句子。
You use lots of adjectives in front of main nouns and then you can add interesting stuff.
你在主要名词前面使用了很多形容词，然后你可以添加有趣的东西。
You can say who lives here you can say how long they've lived here but if you start with that in many
你可以说谁住在这里你可以说他们在这里住了多久但如果你从很多人开始
cases it will be more confusing and people will go huh.
情况会更加混乱，人们会去呵呵。
What's he talking about.
他在说什么。
Who's living here.
谁住在这里。
Where are they living.
他们住在哪里。
What.
什么。
So let's look at how we can put it all together.
因此，让我们看看如何将它们组合在一起。